timetemperature.com 2011-01-09

# Privacy

**TimeTemperature.com Privacy Policy** Thank you for visiting the www.timetemperature.com website and reviewing our privacy statement. Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website:

 **Information Collected and Stored Automatically** If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

   1.The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;   
   2.The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;   
   3.The date and time you access our site;   
   4.The pages you visit; and   
   5.If you linked to the www.timetemperature.com website from another website, the address of that website. 

We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors - to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors are using. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits. 

**If You Send Us Personal Information** If you choose to provide us with personal information, as in an email or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us locate for you the information you have requested. We treat e-mails the same way that we regard letters mailed to www.TimeTemperature.com. We do not collect personal information for any purpose other than to respond to you. We only share the information you give us with another government agency, company or individual if your inquiry relates to that entity, or as otherwise required by law. Moreover, we do not create individual profiles with the information you provide or give it to any private organizations.

 **When You Visit other www.timetemperature.com, Inc. Websites** Please read the Privacy Statement when you visit those websites. Where neccessary, other web sites which are owned or operated by www.timetemperature.com, Inc.may have additional privacy criteria, conditions, or information that you should know.

 **Links to Other Sites** Our website has text and graphical links to other web sites, companies and governmental agencies. Once you access another site through a link that we provide you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

 **Ad Servers** We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information. We have no control over the information collected by such ad servers or how that information is used

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Tribal Fusion, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Users may opt out of the use of the Tribal Fusion cookie by visiting the Network Advertising Initiatives [cookie opt-out page.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)  Tribal Fusion is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (the "NAI") and is committed to maintaining compliance with the NAI's Self-Regulatory Principles.

 **Website Security**    1.For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.   
   2.Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used for no other purposes.   
   3.Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act. 

**Comments or Questions** If you have any comments or suggestions about the information presented here please 

[contact](http://www.timetemperature.com/contact.html) us.
